原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译      如是我闻  木浅薰  五天
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第一集
对折
Fold down that...
然后往上折
and then up that...
这个翻过来
and this and over there
你就能得到一个漂亮的天鹅
and you have a beautiful swan!
什么鬼
What the...?!
垃圾自己收拾干净
与安格·沃特金斯一起阻截傻逼
我是安格·沃特金斯  你现在正在收看的是
This is Anger Watkins, and you're watching basic cable's
有线电视台里最愤怒的体育节目
angriest sports show.
兄弟们  这句话难以出口
Folks, this is difficult to say,
但今天  我很愤怒
but, today, I'm angry!
我喜欢他愤怒的样子
I like how angry he is.
与安格·沃特金斯一起阻截傻逼
我想提一个话题
I want to broach a topic
别人都没法在节目上有时间讨论
that no one else has the airtime to fill to discuss.
所有时代中最杰出的人物
Greatest of All Time.
勒布朗  科比还是迈克尔·乔丹
LeBron, Kobe or MJ?
我来告诉你们为什么这些答案都是错的
I'll tell you why you're all wrong!
我们来接通观众吧
Let's open the lines.
制作人说我要接通了
The producer says I'm gonna go on.
拜托了  体育界的耶稣
Please, Sports Jesus,
引导我胡言乱语
guide my blather.
欢迎致电美国愤怒
Welcome to Rage Nation.
你他妈什么毛病
What the hell is your problem?
我第一次看节目
Uh, first-time listener,
打了很久的电话
long-time caller.
所以我
So, I, uh...
给我一个观点
Give me a take!
安格需要一个观点
Anger needs a take.
谁是第一
Who is number one?
约翰·斯托克顿
Uh, John Stockton!
与安格·沃特金斯一起阻截傻逼
正在接通: 侯默·辛普森  春田镇  美国
约翰·斯托克顿
John Stockton?!
我们正在进行日常对话
We're trying to have our daily conversation
一遍遍选出三个最受崇拜的时代爱康
in which we rank and re-rank three demigods,
你却提名约翰·没名没姓·斯托克顿混淆视听
and you bring John "Never Won a Title" Stockton into the mix?!
真可耻  太可耻了
Shame! For shame!
再您妈的见
Dodbye.On!
侯默  你被冲走了
Homer, you got flushed.
不懂体育的男人
A man who don't know sports,
算不上什么男人
um, he ain't much of a man.
你对我来说一无是处
You're nothing to me now.
只是一个丈夫和父亲
Just a husband and father.
傻比安格·沃特金斯
Stupid Anger Watkins
用声效把我冲走了
flushing me with an audio effect.
为什么不把坏情绪合着烤串吃掉呢
Why not eat your feelings with a cheer-up kebab?
来看看  披萨切片
Let's see. Pizza slice,
夏日香肠
summer sausage...
来吧
Here you go.
只是个愚蠢的电话互动节目
It was only a dumb call-in show.
你说的挺容易
Easy for you to say.
如果那个混蛋不喜欢你的体育观点
If that jerk didn't like your sports notions,
听听别人的意见
listen to someone else.
网上都是自制体育节目
The Internet's full of homemade sports shows.
随便谁都能放一个上去
Anyone could put one on,
我是说  即便是  别说"你"
I mean, even... Don't say "You."
别说"你"
Don't say "You."
即便是你
Even you.
妈的
Damn it.
当然了  是的
Oh, yes. Of course!
一档网络体育脱口秀
An Internet sports talk show!
但我去哪里找一个
But where could I find a host
完全赞同我的观点的主持人呢
who thinks all my opinions are great?
就是我自己
Me.
马姬  准备庆祝烤串
Marge, prepare a congratulations kebab.
土豆小孩
这些跟石头一样硬
These are hard as rocks.
食物大战
Food fight!
这号召我们大规模反击
Uh, this calls for massive retaliation.
用你们的二次方程  兄弟们
Use your quadratic equations, men.
老天  我出现幻觉了
Oh, my God. I'm having a flashback.
上帝  我重来了遍新春攻势[越战战役]
Good Lord, I'm reliving the Tet Offensive.
史金纳
Skinner...
我用海姆利克氏操作法救你
I'll Heimlich you, sir.
请保持不动  我从后面抱你
Just be still so I can embrace you from behind.
放  开  我
Get... off... me.
乖  你安全了
Shh, you're safe now.
回收土豆块
哪个小流氓丢了第一块土豆
Now, which of you little hoodlums tossed the first tot?
-书呆子干的  -可能是丽莎
- The nerd did it. - Uh, could be Lisa.
史金纳校长  不是我  是物理现象[菲克斯]
Principal Skinner, it wasn't me. It was physics.
是真的吗  菲克斯
Is this true, Fizix?
我以为来自土库曼的交换生表现良好呢
I would've thought better of a Turkemenistan exchange student.
我与此事无关
Ah! I had nothing to do with it.
我来这个国家是为了躲避因为食物引发的暴力
I came to this country to escape food-based violence.
丽莎  一周留堂
Lisa, one week's detention.
举止不当
《再见本垒打》[homer=home]
侯默·辛普森出品
再见
欢迎来到《再见本垒打》
Welcome to Walkoff Homer!
我是侯默·辛普森
This is Homer Simpson,
由管上最粗鲁的大兄弟
the rudest dude on the InnerTube.
人们说穆罕默德·阿里是最棒的拳王
They say Muhammad Ali was the greatest of all time,
但他没有跟卡休斯·克雷较量过
but he never fought Cassius Clay.
他害怕什么
What was he afraid of?
爆炸了吧
Boom! Hot take.
还有为什么在篮球界
And how come, in basketball,
他们一直用篮筐
they use the basket all the time
但你踢球的时候真的可以不用脚[指橄榄球]
but you could literally play football without any feet?
这节目太糟糕了
This show sucks.
真不敢相信他把弗兰德斯的无线网浪费在这上
I can't believe he's wasting Flanders' Wi-Fi on this.
《再见本垒打》
侯默·辛普森出品
驼鹿屎
有一些事情一直在困扰着我
Here's a few things that bug me.
他们怎能对主场球队说走步
How can they call traveling on a home team?
为什么足球运动员都这么蠢
Why is soccer so stupid?
在花园里怎么玩曲棍球
How can they play hockey in a garden?
为什么高尔夫运动员不能自己拿球杆
Why can't golfers carry their own clubs?
一群懒蛋
Lazy jerks.
驼鹿屎
"Moose Poo"?!
为什么  你个搞笑的
Why, you hilarious...
尝尝日落玫瑰
Eat Sunset Rose!
半哑光的
Semi-gloss.
种子铃铛
Seed bell?
好像玩意能阻止我似的
Like that's gonna stop me.
太可爱了
Oh, so cute!
看看
Look at...
我的脸  我的脸
Oh, my face! My face!
什么鬼东西这么好笑
What the hell's so funny?
海平面上升
我们一定要齐心协力
We must come together...
降低我们的碳...
to lower our carbon...
-破孩子  -傻老爸
- Stupid boy. - Dumb dad.
首先  他毁了我的生活
First, he ruins my life.
-然后他又毁了我的直播  -我对他直播的破坏
- Then he ruins my livestream. - Me ruining his show was
-就是他直播的唯一看点  -我要靠自己的主意
- the only good part of his show. - I'm gonna change the NHL
-改变曲棍球界  -这是他唯一不错的观点
- with my idea - Fat goalie was his only good take.
-对病态肥胖守门员的看法  -应该当做开端
- for morbidly obese goalies. - Should've led with it.
你们好  话题  第一印象
Hello. #FirstImpression.
天呐  是个网红
Oh, my God, a hipster!
马姬  给他拿瓶微酿啤酒
Marge, bring him a microbrew!
-快  -马上就来
- Quick! - I'm on it!
冲击平原的啤酒花真的有河岸湿地般的苦涩感
The alluvial hops really bring out the riparian bitterness.
他喜欢
He likes it.
-我以为  -我确实喜欢
- I think. - I did like it.
我是沃伯顿·帕克
My name's Warburton Parker.
你们不认识我  不如听我讲讲
I'm a stranger to you. Why should you listen to me?
你们不了解我背景
You don't know my backstory.
开始讲了  冒号
Well, here it is-- colon--
小的时候  我唯一的朋友就是我的电脑
as a child, my only friend was my computer.
我每天都被嘲笑
I was teased every day.
然后我成为了一名滑雪运动员
Then I became a pro snowboarder,
娶了超模  进军科技领域
married a supermodel, went into tech,
赚了一大笔  买下了那些
made a fortune, bought the factories
嘲笑我的人他们的父母工作的工厂
where the kids who teased me's parents worked
然后关停了工厂
and shut the factories down.
你有什么背景故事吗
Do you have a backstory?
有一次  我六岁的时候  我吃了个收音机
Once, when I was six, I ate a radio.
我喜欢你
I like you,
但这不行
but that won't get in the way.
我就直说了吧
Let me cut to the chase.
我靠爆红的视频赚钱
I make money from viral videos.
你们两个已经爆红了
And you two have gone viral.
"旋转门里的小浣熊"  爆
"Raccoon in a revolving door" Viral.
不要起诉我们  背包小孩
你们的确应该跳这种舞
You're right to dance in such a fashion.
因为我即将教你们如何制作
Because I'll show you how to make videos
能让你们富有的视频
that will make you rich.
让我更富有
And me richer.
让我我最富有
And me richest.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
只要有人富了我就会收到提示
I get an alert whenever anyone's getting rich.
五百七十万播放量
5.7Million views!
很好  但算不上优秀
Wow! Good, not great.
科罗拉多州的总人口而已
That's the population of Colorado.
是野马队的那个州吗
Is that the Broncos one?
是的
It is.
问题在于  你们赚了多少钱
The question is, how much money have you made?
我来看看  第三季度花了
Let's see. Uh, third quarter take...
-开销的费用  -当然
- Factor in overhead. - Of course.
-开销  -预估
- Overhead. - Projections.
买纸
苹果到苹果
Apples to apples.
计算净利润
Figure net profit.
算出来了  一个子都没挣
Got it. Nothing.
这是个反问句  你个蠢货
The question was rhetorical, you idiots.
抱歉说你们蠢货
Sorry about the "idiots" thing.
但是你们需要做的就是变现
But what you need to do is monetize.
-变现  变现  -变现  变现
- Monetize! Monetize! - Monetize! Monetize!
单轨铁路  单轨铁路
Monorail. Monorail.
等等  我们在说什么
Wait, what are we talking about?
即将呈现
油管有史以来最出色的视频
猴子闻了手指然后从树上摔下去
也许你们很熟悉
Perhaps you are familiar
有史以来传播最广的视频
with the greatest viral video of all time,
猴子闻了手指然后从树上摔下去
"Monkey smells finger and falls out of tree."
不  我从来没看过
No, I've never seen...
我的...
Oh, my... Oh...
那只猴子
Oh, that monkey!
45分钟之后
这个  这个猴子
And the-the monkey!
闻了自己的手指
He smelled his finger.
一小时之后
然后  晕过去了
Then boom!
闻
Smell.
那只猴子以及他的团队
That monkey and that monkey's estate
一分钱都没挣
made zero dollars.
连猴币都没挣到
Even less in monkey dollars.
如果他和我签约了
If he had signed with me,
只是做个假设
I mean, just hypothetically,
那么将会有  我说不准
there would be-- oh, I don't know--
猴子嗅手指T恤
Monkey Finger Sniff T-shirts,
猴子嗅手指擦手巾
Monkey Finger Sniff Finger Wipes,
猴子嗅手指赞助商
Monkey Finger Sniff sponsorships
还能在周六夜现场占上一席之地
and a spot on Weekend Update on SNL.
主持人会是拉米·马雷克  或者更好的
Host, Rami Malek or better.
配乐嘉宾是皮特卜
Musical guest, Pitbull.
这只猴子没嗅到机会的气息
What this monkey didn't sniff was opportunity.
接下来的五分钟里  你们的浏览量
In the next five minutes, you'll get more views
将比整季墨菲·布朗续集加起来还要高
than the entire rebooted Murphy Brown.
我对这剧的期望可高了
Ugh, such high hopes.
艾尔丁不在了就完全不一样了
Not the same without Eldin.
这次录像  你们的赞助商会是
Now, this fight, you're gonna get kickback from...
-达夫啤酒吗  -看看你的T恤
-Duff Beer? -Look at your shirt.
巴斯可乐
商标对准镜头
Label to camera.
Hey, label to camera.
他们会喜欢这次宣传的
They're gonna love this publicity.
你们刚刚挣到了第一个四分之一
You guys just earned your first quarter.
第一个四分之一财年的任务指标吗
First quarter revenue?
不是  是挣了第一个四分之一美元
No. First quarter, like the coin.
奔腾年代  兄弟
Halt and Catch Fire, boy!
硅谷纪实
Silicon Valley!
奔腾年代和硅谷纪实都是描述网络科技创业的电视剧
互联网就是这么赢的
How the Web Was Won.
再给你四分之一美元  请你闭嘴
I'll give you another quarter to shut up.
变现
Monetize.
春田小学
禁闭室
瞧我们
Look at us,
校园恶霸
the bully,
学园交际花
the princess,
更多的恶霸
more bullies,
拉尔夫
the Ralph
还有我  无人理解的天才儿童
and me, the smart kid no one gets.
然而  也许到最后
Yet, maybe, by the end of the day,
我会发现这才是我想要的
I'll realize this is just what I needed.
这正是我需要用来打破
This is what I needed to break through the...
丽莎  你不属于这里
Lisa, you don't belong here.
感谢上帝  再见了失足青年们
Oh, thank God. So long, delinquents!
你的禁闭室是新开的  远现矫中心
Your detention is being held in our new facility, the R.O.C.C.
欢迎来到远程现场行为矫正中心
Welcome to the Remote On-site Correctional Center.
一个地方怎么可能又是远程又是现场
How can something be both remote and on-site?
好了  温斯海默
All right, Wisenheimer.
你刚刚为自己赢得了叛少管一日游
You just earned yourself a day in the HOLE.
也就是叛逆少年管教中心一日游
The Holistic Obstinance Lessening Environment.
这除了古董鸡皮疙瘩系列书之外啥也没有
There's nothing in here but old Goosebumps books.
很好  读完这些书
Fine. Read those.
这些书一点都不吓人  一点不吓人
They aren't scary. They aren't scary!
平常用的禁闭室怎么了
What happened to regular detention?
因为我们已经没有资金
Well, because we could no longer afford
可以由来偿付任何课外活动
any after-school activity,
学校把禁闭室外包出去了
the school district has outsourced detention.
欢迎来到不良行为矫正中心
Welcome to Misbehavior Solutions,
世界酷刑五百强公司
a Torture 500 company.
你把禁闭室私有化了吗
You privatized detention?
丽莎  你要理解
Lisa, you have to understand.
任何有一点小穷的人
Anyone who's done anything remotely poor
都在私人监狱里
is in private prison.
我提到穷了吗  我想说的是犯了小错的人
Oh, did I say "Poor"? I meant wrong.
不准再提问了
No more questions.
变现计划怎么样了
So, how's the monetizing going?
选一只手
Pick a hand.
再选一次
Pick again.
别选同一只
Not the same hand.
我可不是魔术师  在另一只手里
I'm not a magician. It's in the other hand.
快选另一只手
Please pick the other hand.
行了  直接给你看支票好了
All right, I'm just gonna show you the check.
老天
Oh, my God!
五千美元
$5,000!
这对我的购船计划会有帮助的
This will come in handy when I buy a boat!
侯默购船记  十一月三日上映
为了更大的变现
Now, for the really big money,
我出售了你们下次打架的场地选择权
I sold the location rights to your next fight.
不行  不行  这事需要讨论
Huh? No, no, no. This needs to be a discussion.
就在这家炸鸡店里
It's here in this fried chicken restaurant.
尤提卡野生鸡腿肉
讨论完毕
End of discussion.
这家店的企业形象有点问题
You see, this place has an image problem.
上周他们这里出了九起沙门氏菌致死案
They've had nine salmonella deaths
还有人在食物里吃出了油炸手指
and one fried pinky in the past week.
沙门氏菌
Salmon-ella.
所以他们想要你们  你和你
So they want you two-- you and you--
帮他们改善一下公众形象
to change the conversation.
如果有一家本地平民化快餐连锁店
If there's a regional, casual dining chain
需要我的帮助  我义不容辞
that needs my help, I'm there!
我的英雄们
My heroes.
好的  只需要  你懂得  假吃
Okay, kind of, you know, fake nibble.
-假装你很爱吃这些鸡腿  -我确实爱吃
- Pretend you're enjoying the thighs. - I am.
这都是蜡做的
Uh, they're made of wax.
无所谓  我都吃四桶了
Whatever. I'm on my fourth bucket.
真惨  好了  开拍
Sad. Okay, just action.
上涨  上涨  上涨
And escalate and escalate.
流量  流量  流量
Views, views, views.
很好
Yes!
感受下热油的威力  真的坐上去
Feel the burn. Literally sit in it.
要来点洋葱圈吗
Would you like some onion rings?
为什么不呢
I don't see why not.
很好  美极了
Ah. Beautiful.
看看这飞速上涨的浏览量
Look at those view numbers fly.
我不该说的
I-I shouldn't say this.
不管  我要说了
No, I-I'm gonna say it.
好吧  我常常这么说
Okay, I say it a lot.
你们俩比马拉松腹泻男还受欢迎
You two are more beloved than Marathon-Diarrhea Guy.
-我很喜欢那个人  -最棒的人
- I love that guy. - Best guy.
有很多打架赞助商派对点我们
We have so many sick sponsored fights lined up.
我们会让马拉松腹泻男看起来
We're gonna make Marathon-Diarrhea Guy look
和洗衣机上的狗一样
like Dog on Washing Machine.
-我很喜欢那条狗  -最棒的狗
- I love that dog! - Best dog.
胡桃木圣熟食店
暴力最棒
Violence is the best.
爸爸  你拉着我的手呢
Dad, you're holding my hand.
很奇怪吗
Is that weird?
书上说这种事有发生过
I've seen it in books.
老谋子酒吧
儿子  要不要我给你买一杯
Say, boy, can I buy you a...?
不用了  不过谢谢
Nah, I'm good, but thanks.
来杯达夫  老谋子
Give me a Duff, Moe.
天哪天  你的钱在这里可不能用
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Your money's no good here.
你现在是名人了  油管大V
You're a celebrity now, Mr. YouTube.
那条蛇吃了三个台球后
The biggest one this bar has seen
这个酒吧来的最大的油管大V
since the snake that ate three pool balls.
我还有照片呢  看到吗
Got a picture of that. See it?
让我为你做什么都行
Anything I can do for you.
任何事  只要你开口
Anything. You just name it.
候默酒吧
没想到你要求这个高
Well, little more than I thought you'd ask for,
不过  你的贪婪我喜欢
but, uh, no, I respect the greed.
我去找我的同类了
Now I'm going back to my people.
你们好吗
Hey, how you doing?
是油管上那个男孩
It's that kid from YouTube!
朋友  我们护送你
You, my friend, are getting an escort.
多可爱
Aw, isn't that cute?
给最壮的那个一把枪  我们这周休息吧
Let's give the biggest one a gun and take the week off.
ROCC
苗浩斯  你怎么被留堂了
Milhouse, why are you in detention?
因为我用了尺子上的公制单位
For using the metric side of my ruler.
好像有点过分
That seems pretty arbitrary.
我为什么要被留堂
Uh, why am I here?
我只是洗澡的时候穿了泳裤
All I did was wear swim trunks in the shower.
他们把犯小错的人都关来这里了
They're packing detention with minor infractors.
但是为什么呢
But why?
企业做事还能有什么目的
Why do corporations do anything?
回馈社会呗
To help society.
我们需要你们做儿童车牌
We need you to make kiddie license plates.
凯特琳
愷特琳
凯特·琳
我需要一百个凯特琳  一百愷特琳
I need 100 Caitlyns, 100 Kaitlyns
还要一千个凯特·琳
and a thousand Kate... Lynns.
我妈妈要来接我回家的
Oh, my mom's picking me up.
她会生气的
She'll be frantic!
她们说我可以半夜再去
Oh, they said I could pick him up at midnight.
你想要牌子
You want something stamped?
这个怎么样
How about this?
罢工
罢工  罢工  罢工
Strike! Strike! Strike!
胡言乱语
罢工  罢工  罢工
Strike! Strike! Strike!
你怎么知道公会的事的
How do you know about unions?
因为历史书20世纪30年代后就不写了
'Cause our history books end in the 1930s.
谢了  几位
Thanks, guys.
你好  爸爸
Hey, Dad!
你好  儿子  我都有点想你了
Hey, son! I kind of missed you.
我好像也想你了
I kind of missed you, too.
父子打架铁杆粉
他们在拥抱
Okay, they're hugging.
抱歉  但我以为他们的仇恨是真的呢
Excuse me, but I thought the hate was real.
自从我看了第二部以来的
I have not been so angry
星际大战系列我还没这么愤怒过
since I saw every Star Wars since the second.
他们不是我的英雄了
They are no longer my heroes!
久美子  我们要换掉漫画大会服装了
Kumiko, we are changing the Comic-Con costumes.
我们要换回之前的
We're going back to our old costumes--
美少女战士和月亮
Sailor Moon and the Moon.
罢工
儿童的力量
主教去世
说你呢丘墨士  说你呢史金纳
Hey there, Chalmers. Hey there, Skinner.
我们要罢工到晚餐时间
We will be here until dinner!
这些小诺玛蕾们拒绝后退
These Norma Rae-sinets refuse to back down.
留堂氛围触手可及
You can cut detention with a knife.
另有新闻  主教去世
In other news, the Pope has died.
选项
橡皮子弹
催泪瓦斯
隔离
本企业与贵校有合约
My corporation has a deal with this school
贵校有责任提供免费的  快乐工人
to provide free... kishly happy workers.
你们最好赶紧解决
You better fix this and fast.
我觉得我有答案了
I think I have an answer.
我认识为了钱愿意做任何事的人
I know people who will do anything for money
只要与儿童无关
as long as it doesn't involve kids--
老师们
the teachers.
萨沙
杰森
*我在矿井工作过*
*Well, I been workin' in a coal mine*
*一直下  一直下*
*Goin' down, down, down*
*在矿井工作*
*Workin' in a coal mine*
*差点滑下去*
*Whew, about to slip down*
*在矿井工作*
*Workin' in a coal mine*
*一直下  一直下*
*Goin' down, down, down*
*在矿井工作  差点*
*Workin' in a coal mine, whew...*
代表月亮消灭你
Take it from the Moon.
巴仔和候默不行了
Bart and Homer have cratered.
我讨厌他们  而且我...糟了
I hate them and I-- uh-oh.
所以  因为人们觉得你们互相喜欢
So, because people think you like each other,
你们已经过气了
you're has-beens.
昨日黄花
Yesterday's views.
比聚友网还凉
Deader than MySpace.
曾是全球大型社交网站  现已萧条
没劲的十五分钟
15 minutes of lame.
你们怎么还站在这
Why are you still here around me?
帮帮我们  没点击量和赞
Please help us. It hurts so much to know
我快死了
that no one is clicking me or liking me.
他们可能对我没有看法
They might have no opinion.
我没法接受这样
I can't live with that!
我本人有一个谁都不知道的具有开创性的
May I make an original and groundbreaking observation
原创意见
that no one has ever said before?
娱乐业是有所偏爱的
There is one thing that show business loves.
-贝蒂·怀特  -回归
- Betty White? - A comeback.
美国著名喜剧演员  作家  电视明星
我们会为你们创造一个
We are going to put you out in front
在大V和时尚人物面前
of some of the greatest influencers
表演的机会
and tastemakers alive.
我们来重塑巴仔&侯默这个品牌
We will remake Bart and Homer Brand.
你们觉得BHB2怎么样
What do you say to BHB2?
是毒品吗  让我试试
Is it a drug? Lay it on me.
是"巴仔&侯默第二"  白痴
It stands for "Bart Homer Brand 2," You moron.
我知道的
Of course it is.
是药片类的吗
Is it a pill?
还是别的什么液体
Or the other end?
这是西半球最盛大的
This is the largest gathering of social media influencers
社交媒体名流宴会
in the western hemisphere.
他是雷管
There's Detonator,
游戏攻略大拿
the Internet's leading walkthrough gamer.
你的支线任务是什么  恶魔
What's your side quest, Demon?
-我  -结束NPC对话
- Uh, well, I... - Terminate dialogue tree.
回到主任务
Return to main quest.
那是莱斯利·斯凯
Hey, there's Leslie Sky.
隐藏白人至上主义的美妆达人
She does makeup tutorials with veiled white nationalism.
粉底液可以选择棕色
For the foundation, we can either go with brown,
或肤色
or skin color.
天呐  是尤尔根
Oh, my God, it's Jurgen,
挪威南部知名开箱达人
Southern Norway's leading unboxer.
先把汉堡盒从袋子里拿出来
First we take the burger box from the bag, yeah.
小心地打开以便再次合上
Carefully open the box so it can be reclasped.
开关扣很耐受
Robust hinging.
有点累
I am tired now.
冬天来了
And winter comes.
我来告诉你们怎么做
And now, to tell you what you're gonna do.
杀戮争霸  在线直播
Mortal Kombat: Live Online.
"杀戮"是"杀死"的意思吗
Doesn't "Mortal" Mean "Dead"?
可以是  但那是种修辞
Um, it can, but it's just a figure of speech.
所以我们不需要杀死彼此吗
So we don't kill each other?
杀死效果会更好
Oh, if you did, that would be great.
但随机行事吧
But let's play it by ear.
听着
Okay, guys,
打斗中
when you're in combat,
肯定会互相残杀
definitely killing each other,
重要的是要提到武器赞助商
it's important to feature your sponsored weapons.
巴仔  你提网飞
Bart, you're promoting Netflix.
明白吗  还有三叉戟口香糖
Got it? And Trident gum.
侯默  你代言利斧身体喷雾
Homer, you're repping Axe Body Spray
还有三叉戟薄荷口香糖
and Trident Spearmint gum.
懂了吗  侯默
Do you get it, Homer?
武器和商品对应
The product things match the words.
听起来很没劲
I don't know, this seems kind of lame.
知道什么有劲吗
You know what's not lame?
你杀了自己父亲时
An audience of 200 livestreams
那两百个直播流媒体量
while you kill your own father.
或者其他桥段  你俩掌握
Or whatever. Feel it out.
我糊涂了  我需要点其他灵感
I don't know, I'm gonna need some more inspiration.
天呐  是你吗
Oh, my God, is it really you?
是它
It is.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
油管主播  INS博主们
YouTubers, Instagrammers,
无家可归的前葡萄藤的短视频博主们
and homeless former Viners,
他们在熊猫快餐互相攻击被大家喜爱
you loved them in their smackdown at Panda Express.
他们拥抱后大家都感到失望
Then they hugged and you were like, "What?"
他们就是侯默和巴仔·辛普森
Homer and Bart Simpson!
我闻到恐惧了吗
Do I smell fear?
我不怕你
I'm not afraid of you.
你的味道有如喷了利斧身体清新喷雾
You're smelling the refreshing scent of Axe Body Spray.
魔鬼诱惑
Dark Temptation.
你的味道有如喷了利斧身体清新喷雾
魔鬼诱惑
网飞
过分纵容编剧个人激情
说不上来  爸爸  这感觉不太对
I don't know, Dad. This just doesn't feel right.
我不想和你战斗
I don't want to fight you.
我也是  儿子
Me, neither, son.
谁能想到不同世界的我们
Who'd have thought that two guys from such different worlds
竟能如此契合
could connect like us?
别再擅自说真情实感了
Quit using your words!
巴仔侯默拥抱视频
火车相撞乘客全挂
《再见本垒打》
侯默·辛普森出品
大家好  我是侯默·辛普森
Hello. I'm Homer Simpson.
这是《再见本垒打》的第二期
And this is episode two of Walkoff Homer.
今日一问
Today's question:
体育谈话节目是在完全浪费时间吗
are sports talk shows a complete and utter waste of time?
接下来的五小时
We will get to the bottom of this
我们会仔细研究这个问题
within the next five hours.
五小时吗
Five hours?!
五小时内我怎么说得完
I can't get my point across in five hours.
我的整个职业生涯都取决于我
My whole career depends on me
从不会结束讨论
never quite getting to the finish.
因为我知道
Because I know...